Mahima Bhutani

UX DESIGNER

Since my early days, I had utmost fascination for different human perception and decision-making process. It was only later that I realised, I want to influence and gratify these humanly experiences. Since then, I have devoted myself to User Experience Research and Design.

I have delivered multiple projects both as a member of a skilled team as well as independently. The projects were in different fields and settings providing an all-round development. I have learnt to be persistent and solve problems in creative ways, while still playing well with others.

SKILLS

Design

Sketch, Figma, InVision, XD, Photoshop; Mobile & Web UI; Wireframing & Mockups

User Research

Data & Task Analysis; Persona Building; A/B Testing; User Interviews; Usability Testing

Front-End Development

JavaScript; ReactJS; HTML; CSS; Bootstrap

Soft Skills

Market Research; Presentation Skills; Financial Evaluation; Team Management;

EDUCATION

2017 - 2019

M.Sc. Human Computer Interaction and Design

KTH Royal Instituite of Technology, Sweden

2011 - 2015

B.Tech. Computer Science

Jaypee University of engineering and Technology, India

Portfolio

www.bhutani.design

Mail

mahima@bhutani.design

Call

+46 72 842 6311

LinkedIn Profile

linkedin.com/in/mahimabhutani

EXPERIENCE

2017 - Present

UX/UI Designer

Freelancer

Designed various mobile apps and web applications for multiple companies as a freelancer

Feb 2019 - June 2019

UX Designer as Master Thesis Worker

Scania CV

Responsible for designing and developing portal using information visualization technique for internal workers of the organisation for better decision making.

Nov 2015 - June 2017

Solution Integrator

Ericsson

Responsible for maintenance of Order Management system for Telecom operators which enables management of customer data like billing, revenue, personal information etc.

2014 Summer

Intern

Kleward consulting Pvt. Ltd.

Creation of an interactive web response system for the admin panel. Was responsible for coding, testing and maintenance of the live system. Released a system currently used by World Famous-Tech Observer Admin.